Merry Christmas. I'm pretty sure that the DOJ are not protecting Donald Trump with all these
redactions, but actually they are protecting the connection between the United States and Israel.
Like that's what this is really about. It's about the very clear realization that Jeffrey Epstein
is a Mossad agent and that there has been incredible amounts of treason and of, you know,
imperial behaviors and acts that have happened on the watch of the United States through this
relationship. And that has been reported by Grayzone News, by DropSite News. However, and I get it,
we are so deeply disturbed by the lurid details of the lucidious acts of these individuals.
However, we cannot ignore that there is a reason why Epstein was connected to all of these people.
And that is the reason why the redactions are taking place. What's going to happen to Donald
Trump now? Nothing. What's going to happen to Bill Clinton now? Nothing. I mean, this is not a country
that has cared about pedestrians. What they're hiding is the fact that this is not the United States.
I've been saying the U.S. is going to be annexed by that place over there.
And I believe actually we already have been.